coolbuddy.com 2014-02-09

# CoolBuddy's Website Privacy Policy

**coolbuddy.com Website Privacy Policy  
**  
coolbuddy.com believes strongly in protecting the privacy of the users of our website - http://coolbuddy.com. We need to collect certain information in order to serve you. But we pledge to use your information only for that purpose, and to share it with other parties only as stated in this policy. This policy will tell you: The information we collect from or about you. How we use that information. With whom we share that information. How you can control the use of that information. The security measures used to protect your information. And who you may contact to update, correct, or remove your information.   

**Names and Email Addresses** Whenever you contact us, we use the information you give us to know more about you which helps in replying better to your feedback. The names and email addresses you give us are NOT sold, compiled into any type of mailing list, or otherwise used for any type of email solicitation. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

**Contact coolbuddy.com About Your Information** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please send an email to feedback@coolbuddy.com with the word "privacy" in the subject field:

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we coolbuddy.com are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to feedback@coolbuddy.com .

**Special Notice**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org."](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

**Changes To This Policy**

coolbuddy.com reserves the right to change, amend, or update this Privacy & Security Policy upon prior notice posted on this Site - http://www.coolbuddy.com. Continued use of this Site after such notification indicates your consent to use of your information in accordance with the changed, amended, or updated Privacy & Security Policy. If you do not agree with such changes, amendments or updates, you may remove your contact information from our database as by e-mailing feedback@coolbuddy.com 

|
